partylite.com 2013-05-17

# Privacy Policy | PartyLite

Information is collected on this website by PartyLite. PartyLite is committed to protecting your privacy and will use your personal information responsibly. Please read below for detailed information about our privacy policy.

**Information Collection and Use**

PartyLite is the owner of all information collected at this site. We will not share or rent this personal information with or to anyone else in any way that is different from what is disclosed to you in this policy. We may collect information from several different points on our website or the websites of PartyLite Consultants, when you make a purchase from one of our Consultants or have other interactions where personal data is provided.

At certain points in interactive communication with us, you might provide us with personal information such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address. Demographic personal information such as income level, gender, and other personal information of yours may be provided by you on an optional basis.

We may also gather on line information regarding your purchases and shopping activities on websites we host (such as those of PartyLite Consultants) to improve the content, ease of use and shopping experience on those websites and to improve our marketing and promotions for our company overall and the websites in particular.

In addition, our web server may automatically collect the following non-personally identifiable information; your internet service provider’s address, the referring URL and the information on the pages you access on our site or on the sites of the PartyLite Consultants since we host those websites.

Personal information that you provide to PartyLite will be used by us for the purposes of enabling a PartyLite Consultant or Leader to contact you at your request for the purposes of you becoming a PartyLite Consultant or PartyLite Host. PartyLite may also use your personal information to contact you to keep you informed of developments or opportunities in relation to PartyLite, or any of its products or services.

We may also use information collected when you make a purchase on line through a Consultant Website or at a PartyLite show in order to process your order or purchase, provide warrenty service or advise you of promotions and PartyLite product news. We may also send you emails with offers from marketing partners which have products or service we believe might be of interest to you.

We do use third party companies to gather information and provide services to us, for example in maintaining and organizing customer information and conducting promotions, upgrading our internet services, sending communications and contacting our customers. Some of those third parties will and do have access to the information which customers provide, including email addresses and credit card information and they may also use cookies on behalf of PartyLite.

We may also use third party providers to serve ads for PartyLite products or services throughout the internet. They may provide anonymous information regarding your visits to a PartyLite website (or that of a PartyLite Consultant) and your interaction with the goods and services which PartyLite provides. They may also use information about your visits to PartyLite and other web sites to target advertisements for goods or services. Your anonymous information is collected through a pixel tab, a standard technology used at most major consumer websites. This technology does not require the use or collection of any personally identifiable information such as your name or email address.

If you have any concerns regarding the use of your information or wish to be removed from our email list, please contact us at the address shown at the end of this Privacy Policy.

**Security**

PartyLite has adopted reasonable technical and organizational security measures to prevent unauthorized or unlawful access to or accidental loss of or destruction of your personal information. Not all personal information collected on this website will be retained. All personal information that is retained is encrypted and all systems linked to the internet are equipped with firewalls and tested regularly to provide a high level of security. 

We may retain your personal information at our local PartyLite office or we may send it to PartyLite’s headquarters in Plymouth Massachusetts, USA, but we will assure the security of your personal information in all of our facilities.

If you have any concerns regarding the use of your information or wish to be removed from our email list, please contact us at the address shown at the end of this Privacy Policy.

**Cookies and IP Addresses**

A cookie is a piece of information stored in your hard drive containing information about you. PartyLite may place cookies on your hard drive to assist in site navigation and to personalize your experience on the PartyLite site. If you want to disable those cookies, most internet browsers will allow you to delete cookies from your computer hard drive, prevent them from being stored, or signal a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or "help" screen to learn more about these functions.

We may use a vendor’s services to help PartyLite measure the effectiveness of advertising and to learn about how visitors to our websites use them. To obtain accurate measurements we may use web beacons and cookies provided by a vendor on our websites. The type of information we would collect would include the specific website and pages visited, and information about transactions made. We may use such data to conduct targeted marketing programs or to determine the nature of our customers and the types of products which each customer finds most attractive.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic data and to recognize customer traffic patterns and site usage. 

**Children**

We do not intend to collect any personal information from children under the age of eighteen. If a parent or guardian of a child who has provided us with such personal information would like the information deleted from our records, he or she should contact us at the email address or telephone number listed at the bottom of this policy statement. We will then delete the child’s personal information from our files.

**Applicability**

This Privacy Policy is applicable only the United States and website whose servers are in the United States. This Privacy Policy is not applicable to any PartyLite Website of any PartyLite company or Consultant located outside of the United States.

**Links to other Websites**

From time to time PartyLite may have a link to other websites of marketing partners or for your convenience. Please check the privacy policies of such other websites which may vary from this one.

**Surveys & Contests**

The PartyLite website may request personal information from you via an electronic entry form for purpose of your participation in sweepstakes, contests or surveys. If you choose to provide the personal information requested, we will use that personal information to administer your participation in the relevant sweepstake, contest or survey and in the other ways indicated in this Privacy Policy. 

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

We will post any changes to our privacy policy on the relevant section of our website when our policy changes. However, your consent to provision of information under the current policy will be assumed to constitute consent to any new policy. By your continued use of this website we will make the assumption that you have consented to providing personal information under this privacy policy.

**Right to access and change information**

You have the right to access, review and change any personal information that we might retain. To access or change personal information, please contact us by post or by email at the addresses set out below. 

**Contacting Us**

Please contact us with any questions about our privacy practices, this privacy policy or the protection of your personal information.

**By Mail:**  
PartyLite Gifts, Inc.  
59 Armstrong Road  
Plymouth, Massachusetts 02360  

**By Phone:** 888-999-5706  
**By Email:** [customerserviceus@partylite.com ](mailto:customerserviceus@partylite.com)
